long time no see.
久しぶり
Did you cut your hair?
髪切った?
I cut it.
切りました
Did you cut it?
切った?
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Isn't your face turning red?
顔赤くなってない?
amazing.
すごい
why?
なんで?
Her face is bright red.
真っ赤な顔になってる
Because my skin is white.
肌白いから
I was just drinking some juice.
ちょっと今、ジュース飲んでたもんね
Wait, what time is this now?
ちょっと今、この時期、何の時期だっけ?
Do you understand?
分かる?
Christmas.
クリスマス
Merry Christmas.
メリークリスマス
It's Christmas, isn't it?
クリスマスだよね
Are there stars too?
星もある?
Not really.
ないね
I don't know.
分かんない
Isn't there?
ないの?
How do you usually spend Christmas?
クリスマスいつもどういう感じで過ごしてるの?
Christmas is at home.
クリスマスは、おうちです
At home.
おうちで
Oh, it's at home.
あ、おうちなんだ
Have you ever cosplayed?
なんか、コスプレしたことある?
Christmas cosplay.
クリスマスコスプレ
Santa cosplay.
サンタコスプレ
Not much.
あんまり
what?
なに?
This is my Christmas present.
これさ、クリスマスプレゼント
I thought this would definitely suit me, I thought it would definitely suit me,
これ 絶対似合うと思って、 絶対似合うと思ってさ、
Norin-chan bought it for me.
のりんちゃんが、 買ってきたんだよ
Wear it.
着て
good?
いい?
yes.
はい
Well then, congratulations.
じゃあ、おめでとうございます
wear.
着る
what?
なに?
why?
なんで?
Oh, here, can you wear it here?
あ、ここで、ここで着てくれるの?
Change clothes.
着替え
picture?
え?
I don't know.
分かんない
I thought I'd like to see you change your clothes.
ちょっと着替えるとこ見たいなって思って
Here, here?
ここで、ここでですか?
Look, the scenery is nice, isn't it?
ほら、景色いいでしょ?
picture?
え?
Here?
ここへ?
Do you hate it?
嫌いなんですか?
I want to go over there.
向こう行きたい
Just here, here?
ちょっとここで、 ここ へ?
I thought I'd like to see it.
見たいなって思って
What do you think?
どうですか?
amazing.
すごい
Well, a little more, first, above, maybe.
まあ、もうちょっと、まず、上、多分、
Better take it off.
脱いだほうがいい
beautiful.
綺麗
It's the skin.
肌だね
No, it's fine.
いや、いい
I'm in shape.
体してんな
That's fine.
いいじゃん
cute.
かわいい
The color is cute.
色かわいい
copper?
どう?
Ah, that's cute.
あ、かわいい
It suits you.
似合うね
lastly.
最後に
this is...
これは...
picture?
え?
That's terrible.
やばいね
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいじゃん
I don't like it.
嫌だ
first time?
初めて?
surely.
きっと
Today, I'm preparing something special for Christmas.
今日はさ、クリスマスの特別なものを用意してるから、
Let's celebrate together.
一緒にお祝いしよう
What do you think?
どうですか?
I have prepared it.
用意しました
cute.
かわいい
cute?
かわいい?
cute.
かわいい
Serve cake.
ケーキ出す
That's a lot of extra.
すごい余分で
cute?
かわいい?
looks delicious.
美味しそう
looks delicious?
美味しそう?
looks delicious.
美味 しそう
cake?
ケーキ?
Eat, eat.
食べて、食べて
cake.
ケーキ
Look.
ほら
Eat.
食べて
like?
好き?
like.
好き
Eat it.
食べてよ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Because it's Christmas.
クリスマスだからね
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
You look really happy.
めっちゃ嬉しそうな顔するじゃん
copper?
どう?
delicious.
美味しい
delicious?
美味 しい?
Don't eat strawberries?
いちご食べない?
I don't eat strawberries.
いちご食べない
Okay.
いいよ
Eat the strawberries last.
いちごは最後に食べる
What's the end?
最後は?
Eat the strawberries last.
いちごは最後に食べる
That's why at first.
最初はだからね
It's delicious.
美味しいです
Hey, it's today, you know?
ちょっとさ、今日さ、分かる?
Alcohol.
お酒
Shall I open this for a moment?
ちょっとこれ開けちゃうか
hey.
ね
Eat, eat.
食べて、食べて
delicious?
美味しい?
delicious.
美味しい
You said you always spend Christmas at home.
クリスマスいつもお家で過ごすって言ってたけど、
Alone?
一人?
With my family.
家族で
With family?
家族で?
With my family.
家族で
What do you do to spend your time?
何して過ごすの?
picture?
え?
Eat meat.
お肉食べて
Meat?
お 肉?
Eat meat.
お肉食べて
Eat cake.
ケーキ食べて
ケ ーキ食べて
Here, have a drink.
ほら、飲んで
Drink.
飲んで
It's Christmas, so let's open it.
クリスマスだからさ、開けちゃおうかな
Say Merry Christmas.
メリークリスマスって言って
TRUE?
本当?
Isn't it Merry Christmas?
メリークリスマスじゃない?
Merry Christmas.
メリークリスマス
amazing.
すごい
copper?
どう?
But this is alcohol.
でもこれお酒なんだけど
Can't drink?
飲めない?
How old are you now?
今いくつだっけ?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳だよ
That's right.
そうなんだよね
So, I'm sorry.
だから、ごめんなさい
Carbonated water.
炭酸水ね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Cheers.
乾杯ね
Shall we have a toast?
乾杯にしよっか
I made a toast.
乾杯にしちゃった
Well then, Merry Christmas.
じゃあメリークリスマス
Merry Christmas.
メリークリスマス
copper?
どう?
That's normal.
普通だよね
Drink carbonated water.
炭酸水飲んで
Carbonic acid.
炭酸
Drink, drink.
飲んで飲んで
I love Christmas with my family.
家族とすごく好きなクリスマス
It's family.
家族です
This year too?
今年も?
With my family.
家族と
You're so kind.
優しいね
Can I join you?
一緒にいい?
It's carbonated water.
炭酸水だね
delicious?
美味しい?
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
It's water.
水だよ
Let's drink.
お飲むね
usually.
普通
delicious?
美味しい?
I want to drink too.
俺も飲みたいな
I want to drink
飲みたい
My face turned red.
顔が赤くなって
It hasn't happened.
なってない
I want to drink too.
俺も飲みたい
Can I wait?
待っていい?
good?
いい?
Did you insert it?
挿してくれたの?
挿してくれた?
I didn't say anything.
俺何も言ってなかった
That, huh?
それ、え?
What is normal?
普通に何?
Is that so?
そういうこと?
You drank it now.
飲んだね、今
That kind of thing, that kind of thing.
そういうこと、そういうこと
That's what it is.
そういうこと
You drank it.
飲んじゃったね
It's okay, my face is getting redder.
大丈夫だんだん顔が赤くなって
It hasn't happened.
なってないです
This is carbonated water.
これ炭酸水ですよ
Carbonated water.
炭酸水
delicious.
美味しい
I'll take it.
持ってちゃうんだよ
From there, let it drip from there.
そっから、そっから垂らして
That's proactive.
積極的だね
what happened?
どうしたの?
So proactive.
そんな積極的に
Did you just put it down yourself?
今自分から下に入れてきたの?
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
Did you eat cake too?
ケーキも食べたかな?
picture?
え?
How cool is that?
どういうのかっこいいっすね
strawberry?
いちご?
strawberry.
いちご
It's cute.
可愛いね
Shall we dress like this and eat together?
この格好して一緒に食べる?
amazing.
すごい
Were you wearing underwear like this?
こんな下着履いてたの?
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Prepare yourself properly.
ちゃんと仕付けのして
It's see-through.
透け透けじゃん
It's transparent.
透けてるよ
I can see it.
見えてるよ
I can't see it.
見えてない
I can see it.
見えてるよ
It's see-through.
透け透けじゃん
Oh, it's already closed.
え、もう閉めてるよ
Bring your breasts closer together.
ちょっとおっぱい寄せてさ
Even from before.
前からも
Oh, amazing.
あ、すっごい
Are you thirsty?
喉乾いた?
I'm thirsty.
喉乾いた
picture?
え?
Ah, legs.
あ、足
Why did you do that?
なんでそうしたの?
Because I drank carbonated water.
炭酸水飲んだから
What?
なんだ?
Suck it up?
吸いとる?
What did you do?
なにした?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Don't you know?
わかんない?
What's on it?
何が乗ってる?
It's impossible.
無理よ
Why are you riding?
なんで乗ってんの?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Here, get your hands on it.
ほら、手ついて
You'll erase it.
消し切るでしょ
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
what happened?
どうしたの?
yeah?
ん?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Your face is showing.
顔が出てる
That's weird.
変なのなんだ
Oh, amazing.
あ、すっごい
It's a mess.
ぐちゃぐちゃいって
Should I take a look?
見ちゃおうかな
Can I watch it?
見ちゃっていい?
I'll look at it through the hole in your finger.
指の穴から見てあげる
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Look.
見て
I'm sleeping a lot.
すっごい寝てる
See something for yourself.
自分で何か披露見てください
Isn't it easy?
なりやすいよね?
Is it easy to become?
なりやすい?
I'm sleeping a lot.
すっごい寝てる
amazing.
すごい
I'm sleeping a lot.
す っごい寝てる
What does it taste like?
どんな味?
I'll follow you.
ついちゃう
First, try perusing it.
先、ペルペルしてごらん
Let's play with pie.
パイで遊んでごらん
It feels too good.
気持ち良すぎる
You've gotten better.
上手くなったね
Well, let's go to sleep first.
じゃあ最初に寝よう
Try sleeping.
寝 てみて
Please take a short break.
少し休憩してください
Are you thirsty?
喉乾いたでしょ?
Eat.
食べて
Can I eat it?
食べていいの?
Can I feed you?
食べさせていいのか?
good
いい
Yo.
よ
I'll give you a Christmas present.
ク リスマスプレゼントあげる
Is everyone watching?
みんな見てる?
Are you thirsty?
喉乾いた?
Carbonated water.
炭酸水
One more time.
もう一回
Tell me it's okay.
いいって言ってね
Is it okay?
いいの?
do you want someone?
誰か欲しいの?
It feels good, right?
気持ち良いでしょ?
Carbonated water.
炭酸水
I closed it.
閉めちゃった
Don't close it.
閉めないで
It's open.
オープンだ
One more time.
もう一回
Look at this too.
こ っちも見て
It feels too good.
気持ち良すぎる
Are you about to cry?
泣きそうなの?
Let's go on another date.
またデートしようね
bye bye.
バイバイ